

Gaby Bell

PROFILE

Strong strategic leader with 20 years + experience in both creative agencies and brand owner businesses. I have worked on some of the most famous brands in the world, earning the trust and commitment of the most senior Client leaders. Obsessive about outcomes over output, I am relentless in the pursuit of creative solutions that genuinely boost bottom lines.

WORK EXPERIENCE



2023-PRESENT

Freelance contract to lead strategy for an Agency pitch.



CHIEF STRATEGY OFFICER: NOW ADVERTISING

2018-2023

Director and shareholder of the Agency.

Key objective: grow and expand the business. Develop strategic credibility and reputation.



MANAGING DIRECTOR: BULLETPROOF DESIGN

(2016-2018)

Managing he 180 strong UK office strategically, operationally, from a client perspective, all as a member of the Board.

Developing the New Business proposition and Reputation-driving Strategy under founder Gush Mundae.



CHIEF EXECUTIVE OFFICER: Hall & Partners

(2018-2020)

Leading the EMEA business across Health and Consumer across 50+ Clients whilst also driving the new business pipeline.

Representing the Agency within Omnicom, taking a leading role within the Omniwomen group.



<u>CHIEF STRATEGY OFFICER: M & C SAATCHI</u> (2013-2018)



Responsible for the strategic output of the Agency and the development of strategic talent within it.

Led key accounts within the Agency (Royal Mail / Public Health England / Peroni /Arthritis Research UK). Key new business driver, responsible for bringing in 2 of the Agency's top 3 Clients.

DRAFTFCB



GLOBAL STRATEGY DIRECTOR: DRAFTFCB (2008-2013)

Responsible for all strategic output on the Beiersdorf international business covering brands Nivea, Eucerin and Elastoplast across 96 countries.

Oversaw strategy that awarded Beiersdorf 2 Cannes Lions for Nivea communications.



PLANNING DIRECTOR: HICKLINSLADE & PARTNERS

(2004-2008)

Responsible for the strategic output across brands such as Camelot, Honda, Grolsch & Johnnie Walker, bringing integrated brand thinking to the well-established direct & digital focus of the Agency group. Highlights on Camelot included the securing of the Lottery License for the third term.



MARKETING MANAGER: IPC ELECTRIC (TIME INC.) (2001-2003)

Led the strategic transition of multiple pure play "paper brands' into media brands (including music, lifestyle, living and 'men's'), putting marketing at the heart of the organisation for the first time and creating long-term growth opportunities for IPCMedia/Time Inc. beyond the paper product.



EUROPEAN MARKETING MANAGER: ELIDA FABERGE (UNILEVER) (1997-2001)

Responsible for the strategic overhaul of global deodorant brand Impulse, reversing its decline through a global relaunch and restoring double-digit growth for Unilever.



ACCOUNT PLANNER: J WALTER THOMPSON, EUROPE

(1995-1997)

Grew from graduate trainee into account planner on Clients including Unilever, Kodak & Allied Domecq.

EDUCATION

Business School, Southbank University London: BA Hons in Int. Business.

PERSONAL DEVELOPMENT

Executive leadership coaching (http://www.leadershipcoaching.co.uk/about-us/our-associates/mia-kennedy).

Boston University Leadership diploma.



Digital Immersion training (Hyper Island Master Class).

<u>OTHER</u>

Languages: French, Spanish, Italian, Portuguese & German.